First of all, there are 4 songs on the A-side of CANTRO this time.
The first one is a little bit longer than the others.
This one was composed by Koumi Hirose.
It's a powerful tune, just like Mr. Hirose, and the song is very cute and perfect for summer.
I think it's a very cute song and perfect for summer.
I hope you will listen to it.
Next is "Ochanoma," a place of doomed love.
It's a song about the Showa era and 2025, and it's also called "Wacha Wacha Wacha".
As the title says, this one is long.
It's a long song, but if you open it up, you'll see that it starts with "Isonoge sakurage".
It starts with "iso no kage sakurage" (the hair of the rocky shore).
It's a lyric that idols don't often think of.
That's what you should pay attention to.
It's a song about a tea room, and it's also about the tea room of today.
The lyrics have the feel of the tea room of the past while also having the feel of the tea room of today.
That's what I want you to pay attention to.
The third song is called Shekinare.
This song is the theme song for the TV anime.
Shekinare is a positive song that pushes you forward.
I would like you to listen to it when you are in a difficult time or when you are having a hard time.
The last song is called "Yoridorimidori".
This song has been performed as a live song since the first live tour.
And now that it's going to be a single, I'd like to share it with you.
It has a lot of fruits in it, such as bright parts of a tea house.
I think it is a song that people of all ages can enjoy listening to.
Do you have any ideas about what kind of music you would like to make?
Yes, I, Kubota, had a chance to stay at a tea ceremony horse with 10 other people the other day,
It was a lot of fun to spend the summer at Ochanoma,
And this time, we will have a release event and a single release,
I hope we can make a fun and wonderful summer memory together with you, our fans, and the 10 members of Ochanoma,
I hope that you, the fans, and the 10 members of Ochanoma can create a fun and wonderful summer memory together.
Personally, I want to have a barbecue.
I want to do it!
With 10 people, won't there be fights and sleepovers?
Fights are important!
We all played cards and had fun as a group of 10.We all played cards and stuff, 10 of us.
How many of you were in the most disgusting mood ever?
How many?
But I did feel a little tense one time during a sleepover,
There were two groups of older and two groups of younger in the bathtub, one in the first half and one in the second half. The first half and the second half.
I felt a little tense when they asked me which group would go in first.
We got stuck, and then the older one said, "I'm going in early,
The younger group also went in early.
Younger members: Was that scary?
I was scared!
But they were like, "Hurry up and go," and they were in a good mood,
I wasn't scared.
They were kind! So kind!
Did you have a name for the people who support the tea horses?
So far, it's just something about the tea horses.
We do say it like we use it for the tea farmers.
Yes, it is. But I don't hear the word "ochazuke" used much at all,
Is it that you don't like ochazuke much?
Yes.
We haven't officially decided yet,
So we would like to decide at some future time.
We don't know if ochazuke is official or not.
Who came up with this? Ochazuke.
We are a TV personality and an ochazuke farmer, so we said that tea is like ochazuke,
So we started to use the word "ochazuke" in our blogs and so on,
We have not talked about it among the members yet.
In K-pop music, there are calls from fans.
I wish there was a call for tea horses, but right now, do you still prefer ochazuke?
I don't want oatmeal.
I wonder what it is.
Something for everyone.
I think you have to get permission from the office for this or something.
With the members.
Is ochazuke OK?
But there is something else, like tea farm horses.
Sometimes we call them "ochazuke," meaning those who support us.You sometimes call them "ochazuke," meaning those who support you.
Do you often hear people say that?
Is ochazuke better?
When we talk about ourselves, we don't say "we are ochazuke" so much as "we are ochazuke".
Maybe the team has it.
It's like when we are swamped, we are ochazuke,
I think most of them use it as a verb.
Nishida, are you okay? Are you feeling okay?
I'm fine.
Do you have a preference for one or the other?
Am I allowed to decide?
I'm just asking for your opinion.
But surely, what do you call a business card that refers to you?
First person.
When I refer to myself in the first person, I feel a little uncomfortable when I say "ochazuke,
I also think that "tea farmer horse" would be better when I think about it from your point of view.
I think "tea farm horse" would be better.
But ochazuke is also cute, so it's a pretty hard choice to make.
Yes, you said it is thick and about 300 times the size.
Any comments on that and any further appeals would be appreciated.
Well, I am very surprised that the video of Ai Hoshino dancing in the costume of Ai Hoshino, the star child, was seen by quite a lot of people, and I myself was very surprised,
It was a wonderful opportunity that was prepared for me, so I hope that I will be able to bring this feeling of being on the same level as a good girl even more,
I want to do my best so that I can keep this feeling that I'm on the right track.
Three million?
That's right. You have been in charge of the Ministry of Finance,
It's amazing, isn't it?
You didn't know?
I didn't know. I knew about Airi Suzuki.
I'm sorry, I just need to learn a little more.
I've seen a lot of Airi Suzuki's work, so I don't think I'm losing.
You are?
I'm not losing.